早说过
I told you
我们应该早点返回的
We should have started back sooner.
真要按你说的回去
If we'd left when you had said,
我们就只能两手空空到家了
We'd be returning home empty handed.
怎么不走了
Why are we stopping?
前面有人
I saw someone.
喂  有人吗
Hello?
前面没人
There's nobody there.
有人吗
Hello?
朋友  你没事吧
Are you all right, friend?
你迷路了?
Are you lost?
一年后
ONE YEAR LATER
感应信号增强了
Signal's getting stronger.
这是什么
Hey. what's this?
管它是什么  反正很恶心
It's freakin' creepy, is what that is.
这里有发现
We found something!
我想我们得联系亚特兰蒂斯
I think we'd better contact atlantis.
真不敢相信你要离开这
I can't believe you're leaving.
你感染生病了  我们治好了你
I mean, you're sick, we cure you,
修养了6个月后
You go away for six months to recover.
你终于回来了
You finally come back,
现在才呆了1星期
And now, what, you're here a week,
又要走?
You're leaving again?
抱歉罗德尼  但此时
I'm sorry, rodney, but, for the time being,
我意识到我不属于这里
I've realized that my place isn't here.
什么  你开啥玩笑  你当然是这里的一份子
What? of course it is. what are you, kidding me?
银河系的人们还在遭受病痛
As a doctor, I can't just sit by and do nothing
作为医生  我不能坐视不管无动于衷
While people in this galaxy are suffering,
尤其是当我知道
Especially when I know
我对他们所遭受之苦负有责任
I've had a hand in what's happened to them.
你不可以把这归咎于自己
You cannot blame yourself, all right?
听我说  是迈克尔强迫你帮他的
Look, michael forced you to help him.
撒播毒药的罪魁祸首是他
He was the one disseminating the drug.
是啊  助他改良hoffans的可是我
Aye, and I'm the one who helped the hoffans perfect it.
中校
Colonel.
正好可以帮个忙送我一程
Just in time to give us a hand.
事实上博士
Actually, doc,
你得推迟你的行程了
You'll have to delay your travel plans.
我们刚得到泰迪少校的报道
We just got word from major teldy.
他们发现了另一处迈克尔的实验室
They found another one of michael's labs.
你早应该告诉我咱们要走这么长一段路
I wish you'd told me We'd be doing so much walking.
我没提醒过你吗
Did I forget to mention that?
说是说过
Aye, you did.
但你可没说
You also forgot to mention
我们翻山越岭之后  还得降绳索下山
The fact that we'd be rappelling down the side of a mountain.
我腿都要断了
My legs are seizing up.
这是正常现象
Oh, that's what happens
你在r & r好吃好住6个月无所事事了
When you do nothing for six months of r & r.
谢谢  别忘了我可是在平衡舱里躺了2个月
Not to mention two months in a stasis pod, thank you.
才2个月
Two months?
试试800年
Try 800 years.
你的腿就成橡胶腿了
That'll give you rubber legs.
中校
Colonel.
泰迪少校
Major teldy,
贝克特医生
Dr. beckett.
Dr. beckett,
少校
Major.
这是米拉中士  波特医生
This is sergeant mehra, dr. porter,
还有你已见过面的维加上尉
And of course, you've already met captain vega.
我没想到你的...
I didn't realize you, uh--
我的小分队都是红色娘子军吗  长官?
That my team was a bunch of girls, sir?
我没打算这么说的
That's not what I was going to say.
不过你既然说到了这点...
But, you know, now that you mention it...
上级指示我要挑选最为出色的队员
Well, I was told to pick the best and the brightest.
有趣的是她们就是这么挑出来的
Funny how that worked out.
是很有趣
Funny.
那么谈正事?
Shall we?
好的
Aye. yes.
我们正经过该地区时
We were passing through the area
接收到低能量的类似信号
When we picked up a low-level energy signature.
通过三角定位我们锁定了目标
We were able to triangulate and get a lock on the signal,
最后跟踪到此  地下墓穴
And then follow it down into these catacombs.
要走一段路才到
It's a bit of a walk.
原始信号就是这里发送出来的
The signal finally led us to this.
这是平衡舱
Stasis pods.
我是迈克尔的俘虏时
I spent some time in a number of michael's labs
有段时间就呆在他的实验室里
When I was his prisoner,
但从没看过这样的实验室
But this is one I'm not familiar with.
看起来人去巢空
Well, looks like the cleaning crew
好一段时间了
Hasn't been around in a while.
中士
Hey, sarge.
抱歉  中校
Sorry, colonel.
我们能先别乱碰这里的东西吗
And can we hold off touching stuff here?
我可不希望再让
Last thing I need
3吨碎石给我来个泰山压顶
Is another three tons of rubble falling on my head, all right?
别担心
It's all right.
我已经卸除了安保系统
I've disabled the security protocols.
你能成功卸除?
You can do that?
是啊
Oh yeah.
麦凯这小子怎么不会
Why the hell didn't mckay think of that?
他可是天资驽钝
There was no way for him to have known.
但是得多谢他从倒塌事件里
But thanks to the information that he gathered
收集的信息资料
From that experience,
才使我这次顺利绕过安保系统
I'm able to bypass the security protocols this time.
都得到些什么信息了
What have you got?
一些迈克尔在这个实验室里
Well, data related
做的研究的数据
To michael's experiments in this lab--
看起来相当有价值
This could prove to be very valuable.
但获取这里的全部信息
Going through all of this information
得花上点时间
May take a while, though.
没错
Oh, aye.
也许我们应该得去村子里瞧瞧
Maybe we should go check out the village.
什么村子?
What village?
今早我们发现的
We spotted it this morning.
从这向北走不远
It's just a few clicks south of here.
村民可能有这方面的消息
The locals might have some information.
我想询问村民也比
Well, I guess that beats
干坐着看你们查资料要好
Sitting around here watching these guys read.
中士  你留下保护他俩
Sergeant, you're with them.
确保他们别太走火入魔
Make sure they don't geek out too much, All right?
医生  干得不错啊
Nice work, doctor.
谢谢
Thank you.
非常好
Very nice.
你知道我现在最想要什么吗
You know what I'd love right about now?
让我猜猜  啤酒?
Let me guess. a beer?
是小飞船
A puddle jumper.
如果我知道我们要走这么远
That could've been arranged
我就会早安排一艘过来
Had I'd known we'd be walking for so long.
这地区的植被太茂密了
Yeah, well, the area's too heavily forested.
飞船没法降落啊
There's nowhere to land.
再说  当作运动健身好了
Besides, this is good exercise.
帮你强健骨骼
It firms up your glutes and calves.
是啊  再多走几个小时
Great. couple of more hours of this,
我就可以免去有氧运动了
I can skip my cardio-funk workout.
他们还活的吗
Are they alive?
他们处于休眠状态
They're in stasis...
他们体内物理和化学活动
Their physical and chemical processes
暂时停止运转
Have been suspended,
但是  他们仍是活的
But yes, they're alive.
你能让他们醒过来吗
So can you wake 'em up?
还没有准确搞懂
Well, without the proper understanding
他们各自的情况下
Of their respective conditions,
恐怕这么做会要了他们的命
I'm afraid that might kill them.
那你们就继续将他们冰封
Hmm. so you're just going to keep them on ice
直到你们弄明白为止  是吧
Until you figure something out, huh?
他们早已遗忘自己  遗忘了家人
I guess it doesn't matter to them or their families
这和死去又有什么区别呢
Who've probably written them off.
伙计  这可还能来个阴间大团圆啊  你说是不?
But boy, would that make for one hell of a reunion, huh?
我想我还是去周边查看一下
I think I'm going to check the perimeter.
有需要喊我
Holler if you need me.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你不必道歉的
You have no need to apologize,
坦白的说  她也不必
And, frankly, neither does she.
她说的对
She's right.
苏醒让他们重聚对他们也不错
Resurrections make for very interesting reunions,
毕竟连自己死了都不知道的人
Especially when the dead man had no idea he was dead
有个了结也好
To begin with.
对不起
I'm sorry.
波特医生  你怎么想
How about you, dr. porter?
艾莉森
Oh. alison.
Alison.
有什么有趣的经验之谈可以分享下
Any interesting experiences you'd like to share?
近期有没有遭遇过
Encountered any dangerous predators
危险的克隆掠夺者?
Been cloned lately?
没有  但说实话我是刚来飞马座星系
No, but in all fairness, I am new to the pegasus galaxy.
我听说克隆好像都要两年的
And I hear that cloning is more of a second-year thing.
事实上是三年
Third, actually.
等等
Oh, hang on.
怎么了?
What is it?
这跟迈克尔最初制造的
It appears to be michael's earliest version
人虫杂交形态非常相似啊
of a human-iratus hybrid.
有人吗
Hello?
这儿有人吗
Anyone here?
好吧  我们分散开
All right, let's split up,
四处看看
Take a look around.
保持无线电通讯
Maintain radio contact.
遵命  长官
Yes, sir.
维加  你那边怎么样?
Vega, you got anything?
暂时没什么发现
Nothing on this end.
这儿就像刚被扫荡过一样
It looks like the locals cleared out a while ago.
的确如此  我需要知道答案
Yeah. the question's why.
难以置信
Incredible.
据此显示    这些早期的试验课题
According to this, These earliest test subjects
并不是学术上的人虫杂交物种
weren't technically human-iratus hybrids.
它们是其他几种生命形式的结合
They were a combination of several other lifeforms.
这大概就是他停止这项研究的原因吧
Maybe that's why he discontinued this line of research.
难度太大了
It proved overly ambitious.
哦  不
Well, no.
从这来看  这个实验是成功的
According to this, the experiment was a success.
那...这意味着什么
So... what does that mean?
或许  这意味着我们无能为力
Well, it means there's nothing we can do for them,
因为这些东西已经不属于人类范畴了
Because these things in here aren't people anymore.
抱歉
Sorry.
没想到把你们吓到了
I didn't mean to startle you.
我只是想让你们知道
I just wanted to let you know
天就要黑了
It's going to get dark soon.
那么我们是要在这挑灯夜战呢
So are we going to make this thing an all-nighter,
还是...?
Or...?
不用了 中士
No, sergeant.
别紧张
Easy.
你们是谁
Who are you?
从哪里来的
Where do you come from?
我们从那个又大又圆的家伙里来
Well, we came through that big round thing.
我们是探险家
We're explorers.
你是谁
Who are you?
我叫米拉鲁斯
My name is mirellus.
米拉鲁斯
Well, mirellus,
你干嘛不告诉我们这里发生了什么
Why don't you tell us what happened here?
人都去哪儿了
Where is everyone?
都走了
Gone.
为什么
Why?
大概一年半之前
It began about a year and a half ago.
周围的东西就开始无故失踪
Locals started disappearing--
首先是周围的森林
From the surrounding forest at first,
然后是这里的村民
And then from within the village itself.
不管白天
Day,
还是晚上
Night,
他们总是毫无征兆的就失踪了
They vanished without a trace.
谁也无法解释究竟发生了什么
There was no reason for what was happening,
唯一的解释就是
No explanation except one--
这个村庄遭到了诅咒  所以我们决定废弃它
This village was cursed, and so we abandoned it.
那为什么你还在这里
Then why are you still here?
我现在住在隔壁的村子
I now live in the next village.
我看到你们从山洞撤离
I spotted you exiting the caves.
我尾随而来是想看看你们在干些什么
I followed you to find out what you were doing here
如果有必要的话
And, if necessary,
好让你们警惕
To warn you.
关于这些山洞你知道些什么
What can you tell us about those caves?
谣传说这里非常危险
They're also rumored to be a dangerous place,
但你们活着走了出来
Although the fact That you survived the visit
说明并非如此
would suggest otherwise.
你们在那发现了什么
What did you find there?
谢帕德中校 收到请回答
Colonel sheppard, do you copy?
贝克特  难道你们已经有结果了
Don't tell me you're already done, beckett.
没有  还早着呢
Oh, no. far from it.
我们下载了一些关于我们药片的资料
We've downloaded some information to our tablets.
我们打算今晚上研究一下
We'd like to go over it this evening.
可以的话  我们今晚打算呆在这里
Ideally, we'd like to stick around,
村子里如果有多余房间我们就正好休整下
Possibly bed down in the village if there's room for us.
哦  看上去这里是有些空房子
Yeah, well, I think there's a little room here,
没错
Yeah.
太棒了  我们这就过去
Great. we're headed your way, then.
抱歉了
Sorry about that.
你们要待在这的话我只能祝你们好运了
I wish you luck,If you're planning to stay.
等等
Whoa, whoa.
我们还没聊完呢
We're not finished with this conversation.
天就要黑了  这里可不是什么安全的地方
Night is falling and this isn't a safe place.
我得走了
I must go.
好吧  随你了
All right, suit yourself.
那么  中士
So, sergeant,
听说你在转移之前在星门服役
I hear you served with stargate command before transferring over.
对
Yeah,
但飞马星系上有更多我要找的东西
But pegasus had more of what I was looking for.
你是指什么
And what was that?
那些等待制裁的坏人
Bad guys who need killin'.
在奥利一伙被收拾之后
The milky way just hasn't been the same,
银河系已经不是这样了
since the ori got their butts kicked.
哦  有人可不觉得
Well, some would argue
现在的情况已经好多了
That the situation has actually improved--
怎么
What is it?
我听到了些动静
I thought I heard something.
什么
What?
或许没什么
It's probably nothing.
天啊
Jeez.
好了  我们要向下一个村庄进发了
All right, we're going over to the next village
去跟一些当地居民谈谈
To talk to some locals.
你们需要点什么吗
You guys need anything?
需要什么
Want anything?
如果你刚巧路过星巴克
Yeah, if you happen to pass a starbucks,
帮我带一大杯加三倍糖的香草拿铁
I'll take a grande triple sugar-free vanilla latte.
没问题  中士?
No problem. sarge?
我又要留守了  好吧  长官
I'm babysitting. yes, sir.
我们过几小时就回来
Be back in a couple of hours.
这感觉就像回到大学时代
I feel like I'm back in college
那些为期中考试奋战的日子
Studying for my mid-terms.
深有同感
I know what you mean.
你哪所大学的
Where was that, then?
加州理工大学
Cal tech.
海狸队加油
Go beavers.
是啊
Aye.
你哪年毕业
What year did you graduate?
噢  你还挺年轻的
Oh! so you're just a youngster.
呵呵  谢谢
Oh, thank you.
我只是看到些有趣的东西
I just read something funny.
是很明显的笑话
And really obvious.
不管怎样
Anyway...
什么驱使你来到人马星系
What brings you here to the pegasus galaxy?
这就得归结到我的冒险情结上来
Well, you can just chalk that up to my sense of adventure.
探索陌生领域和未知世界的欲望
A desire to visit strange, unexplored worlds,
和各种新鲜有趣的人类打交道
Meet new and interesting people.
好吧  我去四周巡视下
Okay, I'm going to go check the perimeter.
20分钟后回来
Be back in 20.
除非你们在门把手上挂只袜子
Unless there's a sock on the doorknob.
她很有个性的  是那种
She's a character, that one.
是啊
Yeah.
这雾起的好快啊
This fog sure rolled in quickly.
维加  你确定我们没走错方向么
Vega, are you sure we're heading in the right direction?
差不多吧
More or less.
噢  见鬼
Oh, dammit!
太好了  我的也没电了
Oh, great. mine too.
这雾阻挡了光线
So, the fog's messing with the lights.
让人根本不知道我们这是走在哪
Makes you wonder what we're walking through.
或是呼吸着什么
Or breathing.
怎么了
What's the matter?
我好像看到了什么东西
I think I saw something.
什么
What?
好吧  我也确定看到了些东西
Okay. I definitely saw something that time.
见鬼
Damn.
真吓人
Creepy.
可能只是某种动物
It's probably just some animal.
只是些貌似在跟踪我们的动物?
Just some animal that seems to be stalking us?
真让我心安啊
What a relief.
安静  我好像听到些什么
Quiet. I heard something--
-等等!  -留神  米拉鲁斯.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa! easy, mirellus.
怎么了你
What's going on?
恶魔
Demons!
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
他们出现了  在这雾里
They're out there, in the mist.
恶魔?  是啊
Demons? right.
他们在追我
They're after me.
我们都很危险
All of us are in danger.
放松点
Take it easy.
出于我们的本职
With all due respect,
还是不要相信这套吧
We're not buying any of this, are we?
维加  提高警惕
Stay sharp, vega.
我们还是尽早回去亚特兰蒂斯--
Well, let's get back to atlantis before the--
维加
Vega!
Vega?
真该死
Crap.
撤退
Fall back!
真高兴我们能有机会
I'm really glad That we got this opportunity
一起合作  卡森
to work together, carson.
我也是  艾莉森
So am i, alison.
那是什么
What was that?
我也不知道
I don't know.
中校  一切都好吗
Colonel, is everything all right?
中校  收的到吗  中校
Colonel, do you read? colonel!
无线电信号断了
I'm getting nothing on the radio.
你们到里面去  我到外面看看
Get back inside. I'll check it out.
我和你一起去
I'm coming with you.
你真以为你可以吗
Like hell you are.
我不会让你自己一个人到那里去的
I'm not going to let you go out there by yourself!
中校叫我照应你
The colonel told me to take care of you,
我只是在履行我的职责
That is exactly what I'm doing.
你们两个给我待在这里
You two are staying here,
尽可能远离枪声
As far away from that gunfire as possible.
现在你快进去  锁好门
Now you get inside and lock the door.
你不能这样...
You can't tell me to--
这是命令
That is an order.
卡森
Carson?
来吧
Come on.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我事前不知道
I didn't know.
你在瞎说什么
What are you talking about?
我的天啊
Oh, my god.
培养仓都打开了
The pods have been opened.
是我
It was me.
我放了他们
I released them.
为什么
Why?
当你问起这个山洞的时候
When you asked about the caves,
我知道你们找到了一些东西
I knew you had found something.
我就自己跑来看看
I came to see for myself.
为什么
Why?
我的太太至今也是下落不明
Because my wife was among the missing.
当我看到尸体都被锁在
When I saw the bodies sealed
培养仓里面时
In those things,
我想那或者是...
I thought that maybe...
我没有想到
I didn't know.
我本以为自己可以救她
I thought that I could save her.
12个培养仓...
12 pods...
说明有12只那种东西在外四野穿梭
That means 12 of those things running around out there.
减去你干掉的那个  也还有11个
Minus the one you took out, that leaves us with 11.
贝克特  波特博士
Beckett? dr. porter?
定是浓雾阻隔了信号
It must be the mist.
我们的手电筒也收到影响
It's messing with our flashlights,
可能现在无线电也不例外了
Probably radios, too.
你的幽灵语好吗
How're your wraith language skills?
应该和你半斤八两吧
I'm guessing about as good as yours.
我们需要联系上贝克特和波特博士
We need beckett and dr. porter here.
那我们去找他们吧
Let's go get 'em.
恶魔还在周围游荡
But the demons are still out there.
我们会回来救你
We'll be back for you.
等等
Wait!
外面已经浓雾迷茫了
It's getting pretty foggy out there.
我们真不该让她自己一个人出去的
I shouldn't have let her go out there by herself.
但是这是她的命令
You were under orders.
我应该坚持己见
I should have insisted.
那她就会采取你的意见了吗
And she probably would've decked you.
你还不是很了解她
You don't know dusty.
那是什么鬼东西
What the hell was that?
可能是她
Maybe she's back.
中士
Sergeant?
中士  是你吗
Sergeant, is that you?
该死
Dammit.
你要干什么
What are you doing?
我要出去
I'm going out there.
达丝蒂叫你在屋里待着
Dusty told us to stay inside.
听着  也许根本没事的
Look, it's probably nothing,
但是以防万一
But just in case it's someone...
我还是带上这个好了
I'd like to surprise them
以备不时之需
Instead of the other way around.
听着  艾莉森
Look, alison.
我没事的  你好好留在这里吧
I'll be fine. you just stay put.
好吗
Okay?
好的
All right.
中士
Sergeant?
米拉中士
Sergeant mehra?
天啊
Dear lord...
来吧
Come on!
谢谢  中士
Thank you, sergeant.
快起来  走
Move it, move it, go!
那是什么鬼东西
What the hell was that?
艾莉森在哪里
Where's alison?
那是什么东西
What were those things?
压低声量
Lower your voice.
我想那些东西是靠声音来辨位的
I think those creatures hunt by sound.
天啊
Oh, god.
看到你们的反应
Judging from that,
相信你们也知道发生什么事了
I'm guessing you already know what's going on?
上尉人呢
Where's the captain?
她被杀了
She's gone.
波特在哪里
Where's porter?
我们也不知道
We don't know.
真好
Oh, that's great.
它们现在只要
All we need now
来招瓮中捉鳖
Is for the prom queen and the kid in the wheelchair
我们就玩完了
To wander off and we're all set.
我们要找到她
We have to find her.
她不知道外面的情况
She has no idea what's out there.
外面究竟怎么了
What the hell is out there?
迈克尔的试验
Michael's experiments.
是的  这个我们也想到了
Yeah, I think we figured that one out.
这是早期的混合人
It's an early version of the hybrid
经过基因变异选择
That's been genetically altered to incorporate
融入了不同生物掠夺的天性
The predatory characteristics of several other creatures.
那是什么生物
What other creatures?
我也不知道
I'm not sure.
我只知道
All I know for certain
他们都是没有视觉  但听觉极其灵敏
Is that they're blind and they hunt by sound.
外面的层层浓雾
And that fog out there,
绝非自然现象
It's not a natural weather phenomenon.
我看到浓雾从他们脖子旁的腮上渗出来
I saw one of them exude the mist from the gills in its neck.
什么  像乌贼喷墨汁那样
What, like a squid releasing its ink?
但是那是防御敌人的条件反射
Except that's a defensive mechanism.
明显那东西利用浓雾做掩护
These creatures clearly use the fog
进行掠食
As a predatory device.
那就解释了实验室里那个防毒面具的问题
which i think can explain the gas mask back in the lab
天知道
God knows
外面的雾气会对我们有什么影响
What prolonged exposure to this mist could do to us.
我有个好提议
I got a great idea.
不要去理它
Let's not find out.
我们应该在这里待到天明  这样准保险
We should wait here until dawn. then it will be safe.
外面的生物可不是夜猫子
Those things out there are not nocturnal.
不管白天还是晚上  照样行动自如
Day or night, doesn't matter.
再者  我们不能干坐在这  我们得找到波特
Besides, we can't sit around. we got to find porter.
你不是说真的吧
You can't be serious?
你要到外面去?
You're going out there?
快去查查那些数据
Get back to work on that data.
找个办法解决掉那些东西
Try to figure out a way to deal with those things.
这可能有点棘手  中校
That might be a problem, colonel.
迈克尔放弃这个试验的原因就是...
There's a reason michael abandoned that research...
他本人也无法控制那些生物
Even he couldn't control those creatures.
太好了
Great.
好了  你确定在这没事吗
All right, you sure you'll be okay here?
只要大家都安静
As long as we're quiet,
我们就没有危险
We'll be safer in here than you are out there.
好的  扩大搜索范围
All right, we'll split up to cover more ground.
8点集合
Back in 20.
祝你好运
Good luck.
无论做什么  小声为上
Whatever you do, be quiet.
这是个错误
This was a mistake.
小声点
Keep your voice down.
我警告过他们  这样做太危险了
I told them it was too dangerous!
小声点
Shh! quiet.
我们该去别的村庄
Instead of coming back here,
而不是回来
We should have gone to the next village.
那就会很安全了
We'd be safe there!
闭嘴
Shut it!
现在我们全都...
Now we've put all of our--
艾莉  你还好吗
Ali, you okay?
是的
Yeah.
我们走吧
Let's head out.
中校
Colonel.
这是泰迪少校
It's major teldy.
她没看见我们
She doesn't see us.
盯着6点钟方向
Take the six.
好吧
All right.
我以为你死了
I thought you were dead.
我也以为你死了呢
Yeah, for a while there, so did i.
其他人呢
What about the others?
他们逃脱了吗
Think they made it out?
我想至少有一个没那么侥幸
Well, I'm guessing at least one of them didn't.
这儿有血迹
We got blood.
卡森?
Carson?
不得而知了
No way to know.
这些东西  就这样从井里爬了出来
One of those things came crawling right up out of the well.
让我想起了些事
It got me thinking.
这些地下墓穴
Those catacombs,
它们向四面八方蜿蜒数英里
They run for miles in every direction.
我想它们应该是直接和那井是连接起来的
I'm guessing that one of them runs right to that well
通到镇中心
And into the center of town.
这就说明了为什么迈克尔可以
That would explain how michael could
神不知鬼不觉的清除掉他的实验项目
Snag his test subjects without being seen.
好吧
All right, well,
我们在实验室里找到12个平衡舱
We saw 12 of those pods in the lab.
在森林里我也干掉了一个
I killed one back in the forest, so--
我也解决了2个
I tagged two--
恰巧让我领先了
Which, incidentally, puts me in the lead.
这样看来
All right, well,
还有9个
That brings us down to nine.
很好  接下来呢
Okay, so, now what?
想到什么了吗
Any ideas?
那些生物
Well, those creatures
听觉系统得以强化
Possess a heightened auditory system
这就使他们不必使用视觉
That allows them to hunt blind.
我们应该利用这一点
We could try exploiting it.
怎么说
How?
我不太确定
I don't know,
或许能够设个陷阱
Maybe luring them into an ambush?
那你觉得该用什么做诱饵
What the hell do you plan on using as bait?
这个
This.
这个方法应该行得通
All right, here's how it's going to work.
你们三个  在高处
While you three are taking up high-ground positions--
泰迪和波特在这边  米拉在那边
Teldy and porter here, mehra over here--
地面行动就由我来  我去安放炸药
I'm going to be on the ground, setting charges.
你要把井炸了?
You're going to blow the well?
嗯  我是这么计划的
Yeah, that's the plan.
那你最好弄个定时装置
Okay, well, you better use a timer.
大雾能干扰我们的无线电和手电
If the fog is messing with our radios and flashlights,
那遥控装置很有可能也会受到影响
Chances are the remote detonator won't work either.
那这样吧  我一靠近那个井
All right, once I get to the well,
我就打开电脑
I'll turn on the computer.
我设定的是发射一个超音波的爆炸
Well, I've programmed it to emit an ultrasonic burst
所以会把他们直接引向你
So that'll draw them right to you.
但是要记住  一旦它们靠近了
But remember, if it gets near the fog--
我就把它关小一半
I'll put it halfway down.
既让它们够不着
That should keep it out of reach
而且作用时间也足够长  好把9个都引来
And working long enough to attract all nine.
你们3个  就位以后
You three, take a position,
就不要动了  直到听到信号
Sit tight until you hear a signal,
然后看到会动的就开枪
Then open up on anything that moves.
那用什么做信号
And what's the signal?
那正是炸飞到空中的井了
That would be the well blowing sky high.
那到时候你在哪里
And where will you be?
但愿能够跑得够远了
Well, hopefully as far away as possible.
那要是不成功呢
What if this goes sideways?
不要这么消极  泰迪
Don't be so negative, teldy.
我是认真的  中校
I'm serious, colonel.
你们站好位子  不要乱动
You take up positions, you sit tight,
等着信号  你不要动
And wait for the signal-- you don't move,
不要发出什么声音  直到我把井炸了
You don't make a noise until the well blows.
中校  那...
Colonel, what--
我想我已经说得够清楚的了  中士
I think I've made myself clear, sergeant.
是的  长官
Yes, sir.
都明白该怎么做了吧
Do we all know what we're doing?
是的  长官
Yes, sir.
是的
Sir.
出发
Let's go.
下面出什么事了
What the hell's going on down there?
还不到时候
Not yet.
该死的
Dammit.
再等等吧
Just wait for it.
你还好吗
You all right?
嗯
Yeah.
艾莉森?
Alison?
她很安全
She's, uh, she's safe.
谢天谢地
Thank god.
什么不见了么
What, did you lose something?
C4炸药...
Yeah. my c4.
中校  我们得马上离开这
Colonel, I think it's best that we get moving.
嗯  我也这么想
Yeah, I do too.
来吧
All right.
快点快点
Come on, come on.
我看见他们了
I see them!
你现在开枪  有可能会误伤中校
You shoot now, you risk hitting the colonel.
等信号吧
Just wait for the signal.
中校?
Colonel?
就这些了吗
Is that all of them?
八...九...
Eight... nine...
加上之前的3个  那就刚好了
Plus the other three, that makes 12.
抱歉  这才是第9个
Sorry, that's nine.
9加上3  够12个
Plus the three, makes 12.
是啊!
Right.
少校?
Major?
中校  你在哪
Colonel, where are you?
在井底  墓穴里
Down the well, in the catacombs.
我找到贝克特了
I've got beckett.
你们三个下来和我们会合吧
I need you three to rappel down here and join us.
马上就来
On our way.
我真想马上回到亚特兰蒂斯
I just want to get back to atlantis
然后好好睡上一周
And sleep for a week.
我了解
Aye, I know what you mean.
我保证这不会太久了
I promise this won't take long.
艾莉森  你还好吗
Alison, are you okay?
还好
Um, yeah.
我能不能留在这里一会儿
Hey, guys, do you mind if I just hang back here?
这一天过得够呛
I've had enough mad science for one day.
当然可以
Yeah, sure.
我留下来陪她
I'll keep her company.
我们马上回来
We'll be quick.
最好能够一次性把这些怪物的数据都弄齐
I want to make sure I get all the data on these creatures,
免得再跑一趟
Save a return trip.
那是什么
What was that?
什么
What?
我好像听到什么动静
I thought I heard something.
放松点呀
Relax, okay?
实验室里有12个舱
There were 12 pods.
我们也干掉了12个
We counted 12 kills.
一网打尽了
We got 'em all.
怎么了
What is it?
噢  糟糕
Oh, crap.
有漏网的了
We didn't get them all.
什么都没有啊
It's nothing.
波特?  米拉?
Porter? mehra?
如果它们偷袭过来
If they overtake our position,
我命令你们俩撤退
I want you two to fall back.
从第2个通道走  回到地面上
Take the second tunnel up, go to the surface,
向星门拨号
Dial the gate.
现在轮你消极了
Now who's being negative?
都干掉了?
All clear?
都干掉了
All clear.
真不敢相信你现在就要走了
I can't believe you're leaving already.
你到这儿还不满两周呢
You've been here, like, less than two weeks.
迈克尔的研究项目
Well, I've completed my research
我已经完全搞清楚了
Into michael's test subjects
而且结果已经交接给lynch博士的团队
And passed my findings on to dr. lynch and his team.
现在该回头关注更重要的救死扶伤的事业了
And now it's time to move on to the more important work of saving lives.
嗨  医生
Hey, doc.
或许我言之过早了
Maybe I spoke too soon.
还有什么外世界事件需要我么
Another off-world situation require my expertise?
我只是过来看看你是不是需要帮忙
Actually, just came to see if you needed some help.
噢  多谢了
Oh, much appreciated.
那  波特怎么样了
Oh, by the way, how's porter?
谁
Who?
她很好  想在r & r待几周
She's fine-- planning a couple weeks of r & r,
然后会回来飞马座星系的
Then she'll be back in the pegasus galaxy.
你知道的中校  像她这样的人才
You know, colonel, someone like her
对我的工作真的会很有帮助
Could be of real benefit to the type of work I'll be doing.
一定会的
I'll bet.
谁是波特啊
Who's porter?
或许有些事情你得跟伍尔希说说
Something you might want to mention to mr. woolsey.
就当已经说了嘛
Consider it done.
好吧  告诉你们
Fine, you know what?
我才不想知道  不要告诉我
I don't even want to know. don't tell me.
嘿  别走啊  快告诉我
Okay, come on, tell me!